<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Dyeislife.DK</title>
    <link>http://dyeislife.dk/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Dyeislife.DK</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dyeislife.dk/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>http://dyeislife.dk/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dyeislife.dk/en/about/</guid>
      <description>The crew   Karl @karlinho   Karl is probably the most consistent player to exist. His table hit rate comes in on 97%. This is what a semester in the USA with every day Dyeing does with you. He is also the only one from us who had to do a naked run (There is a video online).                  Hans @minefifahans   Fifa a controversial part of the game is defended by Hans rigorously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rules</title>
      <link>http://dyeislife.dk/en/rulebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dyeislife.dk/en/rulebook/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer Beer die (Dye) can – like many other beer games – be played in thousands of different variations. The following are the preferred rules of the team behind dyeislife.dk, which we recommend everyone to follow. Dye Up!
The Set-Up  To play Beer Die (also referred to as dye), you will need a 4’ by 8’ (feet) plywood table with a dividing line going through the middle (vertically). It should be roughly 3 to 3 ½&amp;rsquo; off the ground We recommend getting 5 ply pine plywood 1/2&amp;rdquo; (inches) thick 4 Pint size glasses - 1 glass placed in each of the table&amp;rsquo;s four corners 2 Dice 4 Players (2 teams of 2 players) Beer of choice Each player before the game starts must fill one full beer in their cup A full beer (can) is placed in the center of the table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Season</title>
      <link>http://dyeislife.dk/en/season/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dyeislife.dk/en/season/</guid>
      <description>New season, new luck Official Dye season has kicked off. Register by getting in contact with one of us and receive your 2020 certificate card to be able to play.
  2020 Tietgenkollegiet   Dato Hold A Hold B Score     Jul 8, 2020 Jan og Rasmus Hans og Karl 11:0   Jul 8, 2020 Jan og Rasmus Hans og Karl 8:11   Jul 9, 2020 Holger og Jan Hans og Karl 11:3      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shop</title>
      <link>http://dyeislife.dk/en/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dyeislife.dk/en/shop/</guid>
      <description>T-Shirt  The missing piece in your wardrope: The dyeislifedk shirt. It is essential for every Dyer and poser.  250 DKK Buy now       Stickers  The stickers. Go out and spread the word of Dye, plaster it over your favorite public toilet. Please don&amp;#39;t do this–it&amp;#39;s vandalism.  50 DKK Buy now       Hat  What a hat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tournament</title>
      <link>http://dyeislife.dk/en/tournament/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dyeislife.dk/en/tournament/</guid>
      <description>Official Beer Die (Dye) Tietgenkollegiet Tournament Overall standings This table is solemly to give an overview of all participants. Position 1 does not mean winner of the tournament.
  Pos Team Wins Losses Sinks Mines Player Player     1 No time to die 0 0 0 0 Laurits Mads   2 Les deux merveilles 0 0 0 0 Alexandre Eline   3 N/A 0 0 0 0 Daniel Öykü   4 Gøl &amp;amp; Fogh 0 0 0 0 Frederik Rasmus   5 RAM RANCH 0 0 0 0 Marcus Nikolaj   6 Jonads 0 0 0 0 Jon Mads   7 Dye Hard 2: Dye Harder 0 0 0 0 Gustav N/A   8 dye martini 0 0 0 0 Hans Karl   9 Dyelai Lama 0 0 0 0 Jan William   10 N/A 0 0 0 0 Clara Viktoria   11 N/A 0 0 0 0 Sebastian Signe   12 N/A 0 0 0 0 Simon Till   13 Skeltvedye 0 0 0 0 Nanna Stine   14 Bomb 0 0 0 0 Raphael Tor    Tournament bracket The tournament bracket will be announced as soon as all teams have registered.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>