<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on dyeislife.dk</title>
    <link>https://dyeislife.dk/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on dyeislife.dk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://dyeislife.dk/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>https://dyeislife.dk/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dyeislife.dk/en/about/</guid>
      <description>The crew   Karl Managing Dyerector   Karl is probably the most consistent player to exist. His table hit rate comes in on 97%. This is what a semester in the USA with every day Dyeing does with you. He is also the only one from us who had to do a naked run (There is a video online).                  Hans Dyeligence Consultant   Fifa a controversial part of the game is defended by Hans rigorously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ranking</title>
      <link>https://dyeislife.dk/en/ranking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dyeislife.dk/en/ranking/</guid>
      <description>DyElo Rating Here we are tracking the performance of all tournament participants. The data includes only the games from the 2020, 2021 Tietgen Dye Tournament. We are calculating the strength of an individual by using the Elo rating system. Very simplified it means you gain points when you win and lose otherwise. The amount of points you gain/lose depend on your win/loss probability. Further information at the bottom of the table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rules</title>
      <link>https://dyeislife.dk/en/rulebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dyeislife.dk/en/rulebook/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer Beer die (Dye) can – like many other beer games – be played in thousands of different variations. The following are the preferred rules of the team behind dyeislife.dk, which we recommend everyone to follow. Dye Up!
How to play in video  The Set-Up  To play Beer Die (also referred to as dye), you will need a 4’ by 8’ (feet) plywood table with a dividing line going through the middle (vertically).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks</title>
      <link>https://dyeislife.dk/en/thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dyeislife.dk/en/thanks/</guid>
      <description>Thanks You have successfully signed up for the Tietgen Dye Tournament of 2023. We will be in touch with any further instructions and details.
Until then Dye Up!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
